So now Ajay ji will tell you who
can apply as an
agent in ICC Lord's. What are the categories that
can be there? If you see, there are many varieties in it.
If you are an LIC agent, a CA or
you are also an adult or a student, you
can also do a part-time job on this. So that
you will definitely have full support from Verma sir.
Sir is always available during the week.
You
can connect with him whenever you want. You will get two trainings in a week.
You will get full support from us. You will
get two trainings every week. A trainer will
also be specially provided to you.
We will tell you the product knowledge and how the exam will be conducted.
You will get everything that is available. And sir, let
me categorize a little more.
Within the category, you can apply for any
[Music]
Hello, how are you guys? Today
we are going to do a very special and wonderful work.
Today Ajay Kumar ji is sitting with me
from ICC Lord's and
he is very welcome to our studio today. There are many
such doubts, people who
want to connect with ICC Lombard.  I
want to know about IAC Lombard,
what are the good things in IAC Lombard,
what kind of process is there, how can we
generate a next level income for you people
and there is no kind of job here,
what is the agency business,
today we are going to discuss a lot about it and
Ajay ji, who has been associated with IAC Lombard for a long
time, is going to share all his
inputs with you,
friends, it is very important to watch this video till the end
and please subscribe to my channel,
share it, comment, and definitely
click the bell icon, only then
you will keep getting all the latest updates, so
friends, our journey is
starting here, so I would
like to know a little from Ajay ji first, Ajay ji,
tell us a little about yourself, how long have you been
with the company and how is the company, please
tell us a little about IAC Lombard, hello, my
name is Ajay Kumar, I am a
relationship manager at IAC Lombard,
I have been with you for four to five years, sir,
you have been an associate with us at IAC Lombard for 12
years plus, it is very good
but  200 agents, plus we have
agents working here on date who are fully
equipped and well-trained and are
working in our team. Now, if we just
talk about ICC Lombard, Ajay ji will
tell you about IC Lombard,
how big and how good the company is, and
in which segment we majorly deal.
Now, in short, tell us a little about ICC Lombard.
ICS Lombard, do you know, is at the
second position among GI companies. The first is
New India, after that,
ICSA Lombard is at the second position
in terms of general insurance. And
what is our main segment? Health vertical. Our main
segment is our health vertical. So, we do
special hiring for the health vertical. The
health vertical is one of the
best segments in ICC Lombard, in which the
demand is unlimited. And there are many
such things here which are going to be useful and better for you people. So,
first of all, you have
understood that our focus is that the people
we recruit are only
for the health vertical.  So,
for all those who want to do big work in health insurance, this is the ICC
Lombard platform, which is going to be very
simple and very good.
We have clarified these first basic steps here.
Now let's talk about who can be
recruited here and who can
get the opportunity to work. Look,
joining a big group like ICC Lombard is
a huge achievement. It is a big
name and your brand goes with you.
When you tell someone, "I am
from Lombard," they recognize you. You have
a next-level sir tag. Lord
Lombard's Lombards look like Lombards.
Lombards have some special qualities, like
they are very laborious and very
hardworking, and the way they do their work is
very smooth and easy.
You will not even realize what a
great company you are associated with. Ease of
business is there for the customers as well as
for those who are working. What is
called a big tag,
you can get it here.
So Ajay ji will tell you
who can apply to be an
SA agent at ICC Lombard. What are the
categories? If you look at it, there are many
varieties. If you are an LIC agent, a CA,
or even a student,
you can also do part-time work on it.
So, you will definitely get full support from Verma sir
during the week. Sir is
always available, you
can connect with him on call whenever you want. You will get two
trainings a week. You will get full support from us. You will get two trainings
every week. A
trainer will also be specially provided to you. We will tell you about the
product knowledge and how the exam will be conducted.
You will get that.
And sir, let me further categorize the categories a little.
Under the category, you can be for
any purpose. For example, you
do a job, you have some kind of business. You are a
mutual fund agent, you are a life
insurance agent, you are an agent of any company
which is a Sahi group company. If you are
also an agent of health insurance and also
want to get a general insurance code, then  You
can also take it but keep this in mind that only
one code of general insurance is available,
if you already have a general insurance
code then you cannot take this code, if
you already have a broker code then
also you cannot take this code, you have to take special care of this thing, if
you have a life code or a
health code then you can apply,
giving the exam will be mandatory and how much will its fee be?
Only 000, only 000
is the lifetime fee and after that you will never have to pay any money,
this
is the best part for anyone, you can join such a big group, such a big
company by paying only 000 fees, the
list
of documents for which is written here on the side,
you can read out these documents
and you will have to interact with me about all these details
and
along with the interaction there will be some mandatory conditions as well,
we have two mandatory conditions, first whenever the
code comes then what to do, you will have to
log in a policy of minimum 15000 rupees.
And in the whole year, you have to source 12 policies,
apart from that,
we are talking about all this health insurance, the health
vertical, as soon as you log in with a business of Rs. 15000,
you will get two more codes there,
one for motor and one
for SME, you will get full support in motor, the
biggest advantage here is that
you will get three RMs separately, at the same
company, you will get full support from sir,
this is what sir does, but I will do health, you will
get three RMs for motor and SME, those too will be dedicated, if
you need full support digitally
and physically, you will get all the support, there is
no problem and commission,
I will tell you everything in the chart below,
when you interact with me on the call,
I will tell you everything in that, no problem and the
best from the entire industry is that you will get
commission here, very good, very good ji
[Music]